submitplus.com 2015-06-29

# Walkinweb - Privacy policy

Walkinweb, Inc is committed to user privacy in its products and services. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy.

This policy covers Walkinweb, Inc corporate web site. Walkinweb, Inc encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all web sites you visit. Below is a summary of Walkinweb, Inc online privacy policy. 

  * Customer Feedback and Support. 
    * Provides a mechanism for requesting information from Walkinweb, Inc. Also used to tell us how we can improve our products, services and site designs.
  * Email Correspondence. 
    * Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also used to distribute information about Walkinweb, Inc, our products, and services.
  * Event Registration. 
    * Provides a mechanism for requesting information from you to register in special events.  
We will only use your personal information in the ways specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way in which we use your personal information, unless you consent to the new usage.

We protect the personal information you share with us. For example, if you make an online purchase with us, we encrypt your credit card number. Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job. 

Authorized third party agents may also need access to some of your personal information.   
For example, if we need to dispatch something to you, we must share your name and address with a courier company. We provide third parties with only the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so.

Walkinweb, Inc will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

The Walkinweb, Inc web site uses cookies. Cookies help us to provide you with targeted information by measuring which Web site areas are of greatest interest. Walkinweb, Inc also uses cookies when you register for certain Web promotions. In this situation, a cookie will store useful information that enables our Web site to remember you when you return. Walkinweb, Inc can only read cookies from Walkinweb, Inc Web sites. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access most of our Web sites. Some Web sites will not allow you to complete certain activities if cookies are disabled. For example, our consumer e-commerce site uses session cookies and persistent cookies to process transactions. If you do not accept cookies, the associated shopping bag will not work and you would not be able to order. 

We use “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use (as amended for government websites) and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.

Google Analytics employs cookies to define user sessions, which allows for the collection of data about how visitors are using the websites. Google Analytics uses only first-party cookies for data analysis. This means that the cookies are linked to a specific website domain, and Google Analytics will only use that cookie data for statistical analysis related to your browsing behavior on that specific website. According to Google, the data collected cannot be altered or retrieved by services from other domains.

Our website also uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the WALKINWEB INC website. Any data collected is used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

If you choose, you can opt out by turning off cookies in the preferences settings in your web browser. You may also opt out of Google's Analytics by visiting: [Google Analytics opt out!](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)
